Ingredients: 
1⁄2 cup butter
2 tablespoons cream cheese
1 pint heavy cream
1 teaspoon garlic powder
salt
black pepper
2⁄3 cup grated parmesan cheese (preferably fresh)
1 lb fettuccine, prepared as directed

Method:
In a medium saucepan, melt butter.
When butter is melted, add cream cheese.
When the cream cheese is softened, add heavy cream.
Season with garlic powder, salt, and pepper.
Simmer for 15-20 minutes over low heat, stirring constantly.
Remove from heat and stir in parmesan.
Serve over hot fettucine noodles.